[{"question": "Which body part does a programmer know best?", "answer": "ARM"},
  {"question": "Relationship status?", "answer": "I'll leave the relations to the database."},
  {"question": "How do you get the code for the bank vault?", "answer": "You checkout their branch."},
  {"question": "How did the developer announce their engagement?", "answer": "They `return`ed `true`!"},
  {"question": "Why did the security conscious engineer refuse to pay their dinner bill?", "answer": "Because they could not verify the checksum."},
  {"question": "What do you call a busy waiter?", "answer": "A server."},
  {"question": "What do you call an idle server?", "answer": "A waiter."},
  {"question": "[Please Enter New Password:] fortnight**Q:** [Error: Password is Two Week]"},
  {"question": "How many Prolog programmers does it take to change a lightbulb?", "answer": "Yes."},
  {"question": "What diet did the ghost developer go on?", "answer": "Boolean"},
  {"question": "Why was the developer unhappy at their job?", "answer": "They wanted arrays."},
  {"question": "Why was the function sad after a successful first call?", "answer": "It didn’t get a callback."},
  {"question": "Why did the angry function exceed the callstack size?", "answer": "It got into an Argument with itself"},
  {"question": "Whats the object-oriented way to become wealthy?", "answer": "Inheritance"},
  {"question": "Why did the developer ground their kid?", "answer": "They weren't telling the truthy"},
  {"question": "What did the array say after it was extended?", "answer": "Stop objectifying me."},
  {"question": "Where did the parallel function wash its hands?", "answer": "Async"},
  {"question": "Why did the functions stop calling each other?", "answer": "Because they had constant arguments."},
  {"question": "What's the second movie about a database engineer called?", "answer": "The SQL."},
  {"question": "Why doesn't Hollywood make more Big Data movies?", "answer": "NoSQL."},
  {"question": "What did the spider do on the computer?", "answer": "Made a website!"},
  {"question": "What did the computer do at lunchtime?", "answer": "Had a byte!"},
  {"question": "What does a baby computer call his father?", "answer": "Data!"},
  {"question": "Why did the computer keep sneezing?", "answer": "It had a virus!"},
  {"question": "What is a computer virus?", "answer": "A terminal illness!"},
  {"question": "Why was the computer freezing?", "answer": "It left its Windows open!"},
  {"question": "Why was there a bug in the computer?", "answer": "Because it was looking for a byte to eat?"},
  {"question": "Why did the computer squeak?", "answer": "Because someone stepped on its mouse!"},
  {"question": "What do you get when you cross a computer and a life guard?", "answer": "A screensaver!"},
  {"question": "Where do all the cool mice live?", "answer": "In their mousepads!"},
  {"question": "What do you get when you cross a computer with an elephant?", "answer": "Lots of memory!"},
  {"question": "How do programming pirates pass method parameters?", "answer": "Varrrrarrrgs."},
  {"question": "How do programming shepherds count their flock?", "answer": "With lambda functions"},
  {"question": "What airline do developers prefer when they're in a rush?", "answer": "Delta."},
  {"question": "How did pirates collaborate before computers ?", "answer": "Pier to pier networking."},
  {"question": "Why don't bachelors like Git?", "answer": "Because they are afraid to commit."},
  {"question": "Why was the developer's family upset with them at dinner?", "answer": "They forgot to git squash before going home"},
  {"question": "What did JavaScript call his son?", "answer": "JSON!"},
  {"question": "What did the proud React component say to its child?", "answer": "I've got to give you props"},
  {"question": "What did the server say to his client who was having a bad day?", "answer": "Everything's going to be 200"},
  {"question": "Why did the developer go broke?", "answer": "Because they used up all their cache"},
  {"question": "Are computers dangerous?", "answer": "Nah, they don't byte. They just nibble a bit."},
  {"question": "How did the mafioso kill the Node server?", "answer": "Tie await to it and let it async."},
  {"question": "You know what the best thing about booleans is?", "answer": "Even if you are wrong, you are only off by a bit."},
  {"question": "Why do UPS drivers get nervous when their internet is unstable?", "answer": "Because they might lose packets."},
  {"question": "Why couldn’t the user update a file on a shared server?", "answer": "They didn’t have the write permissions"},
  {"question": "What do you do when you can't understand your husband's behavior?", "answer": "man man"},
  {"question": "What do you call a doctor who fixes websites?", "answer": "A URLogist"},
  {"question": "How many developers does it take to change a light bulb?", "answer": "None. It's a hardware issue"},
  {"question": "Why do programmers always mix up Halloween and Christmas?", "answer": "Because 31 OCT == 25 DEC"},
  {"question": "Why do kayakers make bad programmers?", "answer": "Because they're afraid of waterfall."},
  {"question": "What are computers' favorite snacks?", "answer": "Microchips, phish sticks, and cookies. But just a few bytes of each."},
  {"question": "What do computers love to do at the beach?", "answer": "Put on some spam block for protection so they can safely surf the net while catching some .WAVs!"},
  {"question": "What do you call a computer that sings?", "answer": "A-dell."},
  {"question": "What's a compiler developer's favorite spice?", "answer": "Parsley."},
  {"question": "When do front end developers go out to eat?", "answer": "On their lunch `<br>`."},
  {"question": "How do you help JS errors?", "answer": "You `console` them!"},
  {"question": "Why don't parents teach their kids about regular expressions?", "answer": "Because they don't want them playing with matches"},
  {"question": "Why didn't the `<div />` get invited to the dinner party?", "answer": "Because it had no class!"},
  {"question": "Why aren't cryptocurrency engineers allowed to vote?", "answer": "Because they're miners!"},
  {"question": "Why did the constant break up with the variable?", "answer": "Because they changed."},
  {"question": "Why did the database administrator leave his wife?", "answer": "She had one-to-many relationships."},
  {"question": "What did the Class say in court when put on trial?", "answer": "I strongly object!"},
  {"question": "Why do Java developers wear glasses?", "answer": "Because they don't C#!"},
  {"question": "What are the three hardest problems in computer science?", "answer": "Naming things and off-by-one errors"},
  {"question": "What did the fruit basket say to the developer?", "answer": "I hope you're ready for some pear programming!"},
  {"question": "How does a sysadmin keep a fire going?", "answer": "They rotate the logs."},
  {"question": "I love you and I only love you. Does that turn you on?", "answer": "AND GATE: No."},
  {"question": "Why do all HTML emails get blocked?", "answer": "Because they are all `<span />`."},
  {"question": "What did the process say after working in an infinite loop all day?", "answer": "I need a break."},
  {"question": "An Agent died unexpectedly. How was the crime solved?", "answer": "By looking at the Stack Trace."},
  {"question": "Why did the document store go out of business?", "answer": "It had NoSQL."},
  {"question": "Why can't SQL and NoSQL Developers date one other?", "answer": "Because they don't agree on relationships."},
  {"question": "Why is Python like the Soviet Union?", "answer": "Because it has no private fields"},
  {"question": "Where did the API go to eat?", "answer": "To the RESTaurant"},
  {"question": "Why shouldn't you trust Matlab developers?", "answer": "Because they're always plotting something."},
  {"question": "Why did the developer have to quit smoking?", "answer": "Because they couldn't afford to pay the new syntax."},
  {"question": "How does a programmer open a jar for their significant other?", "answer": "They install Java"},
  {"question": "What did the psychic say to the developers?", "answer": "I see dev people."},
  {"question": "Where does the pirate stash all of their digital treasures?", "answer": "RAR"},
  {"question": "What is React's favorite movie genre?", "answer": "Suspense"},
  {"question": "Why couldn't the React component understand the joke?", "answer": "Because it didn't get the context."},
  {"question": "What did XHR say to AJAX when it thought it was being a Mean Girl?", "answer": "Stop trying to make fetch happen!"},
  {"question": "What was Grace Hopper's favorite car?", "answer": "VW Bug"},
  {"question": "What is a pirate's favorite programming language?", "answer": "You'd think it was R, but a pirate's first love is Objectively C."},
  {"question": "Why did the programmer come home crying?", "answer": "His friends were always boolean him."},
  {"question": "What PostgreSQL library should Python developers use for adult-oriented code?", "answer": "psycoPG13"},
  {"question": "What do you call a beverage that is 75% Root Beer, and 75% Ice Cream?", "answer": "A Float"},
  {"question": "What accommodations did the JavaScript developer request at the hotel?", "answer": "A room with a Vue."},
  {"question": "Where do developers drink?", "answer": "The Foo bar"},
  {"question": "Why was the engineer upset when the bartender served them `1` shot of whiskey?", "answer": "Because they thought they ordered a double."},
  {"question": "Why do assembly programmers need to know how to swim?", "answer": "Because they work below C level."},
  {"question": "Who used the internet before it was cool?", "answer": "Httpsters"},
  {"question": "What kind of computer can hold a musical note?", "answer": "A Dell."},
  {"question": "Why did the web developer always go to the wrong hotel room?", "answer": "They were in room 301."},
  {"question": "How do you stop a web developer stealing your stuff?", "answer": "Write 403 on it."},
  {"question": "Why are machine learning models so fit?", "answer": "Because they do weight training."},
  {"question": "Why did Gargamel shut down the internet?", "answer": "Because he didn't want people **SMURFING** the web!"},
  {"question": "What did the command line die of?", "answer": "A Terminal illness."},
  {"question": "Did you hear what the clumsy cryptographer did to their password?", "answer": "Made a hash of it."},
  {"question": "Why are keyboards always working so hard?", "answer": "Cause they have two shifts!"},
  {"question": "What are clouds made of?", "answer": "Mostly linux servers."},
  {"question": "Why did Tom Selleck never git commit anything?", "answer": "Because he thought he mustache his work."},
  {"question": "How does Mr. Potato Head (dev edition 0.0.1) remove his mustache?", "answer": "git stache pop"},
  {"question": "Why can't you use 'Soup' as your password?", "answer": "Because it isn't `stroganoff`"},
  {"question": "Why do developers use mechanical keyboards?", "answer": "To strongly type their code."},
  {"question": "What is a developer's favorite country song?", "answer": "Hello World - by Lady Antebellum"},
  {"question": "Why was nobody given food at the developer conference?", "answer": "It was a serverless function!"},
  {"question": "Why did the developer cancel their dinner plans?", "answer": "They were unable to fulfil peer dependencies"},
  {"question": "Why did the functional programmer finally move out of their house?", "answer": "For(e) closure"},
  {"question": "How do JavaScript developers break up?", "answer": "They always promise to callback"},
  {"question": "Why do developers mixup Terminals and Polygraphs?", "answer": "Because they both can see a lie (CLI)"},
  {"question": "Did you hear about the programmer that was scared of IDEs?", "answer": "They retreated back into their shell"},
  {"question": "What do you call optimistic front-end developers?", "answer": "Stack half-full developers."},
  {"question": "Have you heard the one about the Corduroy pillow?", "answer": "It's making HEADLINES!"},
  {"question": "Hey officer! How did the hackers escape?", "answer": "No idea. They just ransomware."},
  {"question": "Why can’t data engineers become hat makers?", "answer": "They can only guarantee two thirds of a CAP!"},
  {"question": "How did the hippie learn about database transactions?", "answer": "By taking ACID"},
  {"question": "Why is it called the Dark Ages?", "answer": "There were a lot of KNIGHTS!"},
  {"question": "What did the Network Administrator say when they caught a nasty virus?", "answer": "It hurts when IP"},
  {"question": "Which programming language is the shortest?", "answer": "HTML. Because it doesn't have a neck between its `<head>` and `<body>`."},
  {"question": "What good can come of 2989 witches casting a hex?", "answer": "None, it is always 0xBAD"},
  {"question": "Did you hear about the witch who was off by two when casting a hex?", "answer": "They failed to make the target DEAD and made them DEAF instead!"},
  {"question": "Why do Front-End Developers eat lunch alone?", "answer": "Because, they don't know how to join tables."},
  {"question": "What advice do you give to a JS developer who has never played baseball?", "answer": "Try catch."},
  {"question": "Got any funny DNS jokes?", "answer": "Yeah, but it may take 24 hours to get it."},
  {"question": "Why were A & B so frustrated?", "answer": "Because they couldn’t cd…"},
  {"question": "Where do programmer dad's store their jokes?", "answer": "In a dad-a-base."},
  {"question": "Why do Websockets make the best therapists?", "answer": "They are always listening."},
  {"question": "What kind of image saved the day?", "answer": "The HERO image!"},
  {"question": "Why do programmers prefer dark mode?", "answer": "Because light attracts bugs!"},
  {"question": "Does this vaccine contain a microchip?", "answer": "I don't know for sure, but it must be ARM based."},
  {"question": "How do you make a 4D Printer?", "answer": "Take a 3D printer and give it some time"},
  {"question": "How do front end devs like their brownies?", "answer": "GUI"},
  {"question": "What do hackers do on a boat?", "answer": "Phishing."},
  {"question": "What is the most used language in programming?", "answer": "Profanity"},
  {"question": "Why couldn't the HTML list be trusted?", "answer": "There were LI's everywhere"},
  {"question": "What do you call a bee that lives in America?", "answer": "A USB"}]